Guide to the Goodwin J. (Goodwin Jess) Knight Papers, 1896-1988 (inclusive), 1946-1970 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4. Condolences (Box 175?)
  - Roland Tognazzini, Rosenberg Bros. & Co., Inc., SF 6, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Claude E. Bates, Commissioner, The Salvation Army, 101 Valencia St., S.F. 3, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Milton Lester Lowry, 1003 Malcolm Av., LA 24 friend, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Birdenah M. Moore, 498 Sierra, Bishop, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Ted Goldman, 603 N. Beverly Drive, Beverly Hills, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Martin J. Masters, 215 W. 7th St., LA friend, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Don Frick, Jr., California Club, L.A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Henry Montor, 120 Broadway, New York 5, N.Y., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. C. Lyn Fox, 476 Molimo Drive, S.F. 16 (Zell and Lyn), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. John M. Oshmian, 111 S. Citrus, LA 36 friend, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Robert Groman, 1008 N. Drive, Beverly Hills (Lucille and Bob), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Herbert L. Hirson, LA and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Everett W. Mattoon, attorney general's office State Bldg., LA 12 (Matt), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Louie Miller, Visalia Wrestling Promoter, LA 330 S, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - David L. Sefman, Attorney at Law, 612 Walter P. Story Bldg., 6th and Broad LA 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Chester G. Hanson, 1070 Topeka St., Pasadena Helen and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. E. Hammons, 4338 S. Union Dr., LA 17, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - The Sisters of Mercy, St. Joseph Academy, 815 G Sacramento Diar Sisters, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Boyd Wood, 1545 Green St., S.F. (Edna and Boyd), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Miss Gertrude L. Williams, Cancer Prevention Society, L.A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Waldo S. Macy, Iowa Hills, Calif., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Cecil G. Bills, 1476 Whitefield Rd., Pasadena 7 friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - 30 Year Club of San Pedro (Rowena Wheeler, Secretary), 1137 Mc Donald Av, Wilmington friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Bernard Harrison, Rabbi, Temple E. Manuel, 8844 Wilshire Blvd., Beverly Hil, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Harry Huntington Shutts, 4645 Date Ave., La Mesa, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Ed Welch, P. O. Box 506, Brawley, Calif. (Bonnie and Ed), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Ethel C. Tibbot, 404 Pacheco Av., Santa Cruz, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. Charles Brown, Shoshone, Calif. (Stella and Charlie), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Andriola, 363 - 17th St., San Bernardino friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Hiram Hopkins, G.P. McNear Co., Petaluma, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Pierce Deasy, Box 548, Jackson, Calif. (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Madeline and Helen Pardee, 672 Eleventh St., Oakland, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - A.J. Dingeman, P.O. Box 1186, Oxnard (Al), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Chester W. Dunn, 560 Irving St., Cor. 7th, S.F. 21, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Beach Vasey, Legislative Secretary, Governor's Office, Sacramento 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Albert Dippell, President Wilshire Chamber of Commerce, 3974 Wilshire Blvd., LA 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Clayton Thomason, 4139 Jasmine Ave., Culver City friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Gertrude Cahn, 629 S. Norton Ave., LA 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. Wendell Casey, President, Associated Students, 3518 University Av., LA 7, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Gordon X. Richmond, Attorney at Law, 84 Plaza, Orange, Calif, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - RABBI Jack A. Levy, 1112 Sixteenth St., Bakersfield, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Valmont and Virginia Rouleau, 3032 Van Compo, Montebello friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Grace Marston, 1517 -Fourth Ave., LA 19, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. Richard D. Bennett, 2604 W. 85th St., Inglewood 4 (Dick), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Walter D. Forbes, 368 Hazelwood Av., S.F. 12, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Richard L. North, Attorney at Law, 4222 Colbath Av., Sherman Oaks and Dick, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Carl Kegley, 1944 S. Main St., Corona Alice and Carl, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Howard Naylor, 137½ S. Flower St., LA 12 friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Irving S. Metzler, 814 N. Roxbury Dr., Beverly Hills friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. A. Kleinberger, 1302 N. Sweetzer, LA 46 Eva and al, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. & Mrs. G. Dunaway, 5340 Broadway Terrace, Oakland 18 Mary and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Bert Abraham, Bellflower (Louise and Bert), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George T. Slater, 609 S. Michigan Av., Whittier friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - and Mrs. Joseph Raycraft, 1149 Crestwood, San Pedro Nita and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr and Mrs Harry Johansing, 887 Flintridge Ave., Pasadena 3 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - L.A. Post #8, American Legion (Pearl E. Burk, Secretary), 1816 S. Figueroa St., LA 13, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr and Mrs Carl Greenberg, 3028 Cavendish Drive, LA 64, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Fr. Patrick, El Carmelo Retreat House, 926 E. Highland Av., Redlands Father Patrick, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs Louise Ward Watkins, 1105 Park View Ave., Pasadena 3, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - James J. Sullivan, 31 W. Portal Avenue, S.F. 27 (Jim), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Doris Dearden, L.B., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Wm. Dickinson, 423 S. Lafayette Park Place, LA 5 & Bill, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. O. Swanson, 2044 S. Horne St., Oceanside, Calif. Odeta, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - S.E. Briggs, R.R. #1, Barrington, Illinois (Sam), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs Phillips, 65 N. 4th St. Banning and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Adele Vercoe, 2701 Wilshire Blvd., LA 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. David Wright, Hollister, Calif. (Dave and Vivian), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Jerry Welcker 1917 Carmon Av., Hollywood 28 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Eugene Prince, 3421 Pacific Ave., S.F. Wildred and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Morris Albertoli, 2702 Glendale Blvd., LA 39 (Morris and Anna), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Royal Jimerson, 25 State, S.F. 14 (label and Royal), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Arthur H. Samish, 918 Kohl Bldg., S.F. 4, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Ray O. Harper, 1124 S. Euclid, San Gabriel Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Frank D. Bernheim, Bernheim Bldg., Louisville 2, Kentucky, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Henry J. Kaiser, Jr., Oakland and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Hal Styles, Beverly Hills 8800 in Hill, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - O.J. Lacy, President, California Western States Life Insurance Co., P.O. Box 959, Sacto 4, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Willard W. Keith, 715 W. Olympic Blvd., LA 15, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - L.A. Council, The American Legion, Fred W. Miller, Commander, LA 1816 S., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dr. Charles A. Poys, 610 S. Broadway, LA 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Miss Edith J. King, 2227 Bronson Av., LA 18, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Bess Castetter and Elizabeth Clark, LA 231 Witmen Rt. Miss Castetter and Miss Clark, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - B. J. STENNING Friends, Glendale 1302 -, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Josephine Brown and Family, 727 E. Colden Ave., LA Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Lonnie Hull, 1016 N. Orlando, LA (Ada and Lonnie), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - William C. Mullendore, Edison Bldg., LA (Bill), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Harry T. Usher, 860 Chantauque, Pacific Palisades, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Sisters of St. Francis, St. Francis High School, 25th & K Sts. Daeramento, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Afton Heil and family, Glendale Friends 9th, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Ray Tremaine, 159 S. Norton Av., LA 4, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - and Mrs. Fred Weybret, Salinas (Fred and Ethel), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. A. Kofman, San Leandro news - Sen Leandro (Sara and Abe), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - F.M. Shay, California Prune & Apricot Growers Association, San Jose 6 Frank, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Arthur S. Wenzel, 1642 N. Las Palmas, Hollywood 28, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Charlotte Shelby, 144 Adelaide Drive, Santa Monica, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Bessie Hughes, 248 S. Flower St., LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. John Kriger, 128 E. Canon Perdido St., Santa Barbara Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Willard Vander Veer, 5149 White Oak Ave., Encino, Calif. Van, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Joseph T. Monteleone, 883 - 43rd Av., S.F. Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Earl Lake, 8717 Rangely Av., LA 48 (Ruth and Earl), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Oscar C. Sattinger, Attorney at Law, Southern California Gas Co. Bldg., LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Hal Eaton, P. O. Box 122, Leucadia, Calif. Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - The Dominican Sisters, Flintridge Secred Heart, 440 St. Drive Pasadena Sisters, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Richard W. Fewel, 453 S. Spring St., LA (Dick), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Zyg Taube, 8476 Warner Drive, Culver City - Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - T.J. Elias, 6208 Warner Drive, LA (Ted), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. S. Spencer, 249 Barlock Ave., West L.A. 49 (Helen and Sam), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Maxime A. DuPree, L.A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Maurie Luxford, 4432 Talofa Av., N. Hollywood, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Emma A. Von Hatten, 1017 - 30th Street La?, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Grace Hutton, 805 S. Ogden Drive, L.A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - David W. Hearst, Box 2416 Terminal Annex, L.A. 54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Eva Lee Shop, 205 N. Larchmont, L.A. Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Henry I. Dockweiler, 1035 WanVNuys Bldg. LA 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. Milton D. Sapiro, Superior Court, City Hall, S.F. Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable William J. Palmer, Judge of Superior Court, LA Bill, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Howard V. Bandy and Mrs. E. Louise Bandy, P.O. Box 253, Greenville, Calif. Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Karl Miller, Altadena - 2062 n. El Molino ave. (Karl and Katherine), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Raymond C. Ingram, Gridley, Calif. - (Ray), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Cyril W. Mc Clean, 407 Central Bank Bldg., Oakland 12, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Oliver B. Wyman, 625 Market Street, S.F. 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - James A. Guthrie, 399 D Street, San Bernardino (Jim), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Margaret Ellen Gilliland, 3671 Berry Drive, No. Hollywood, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Charles C. Ashurst, 803 Coronado Terrace, LA 26 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. and Mrs. B.F. Vandenberg, Jr., Bank of America, Sacramento (Jane and Van), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Ben Stone, 123 S. Sweetzer, LA 48 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. John Walton Dinkelspiel, 333 Montgomery St., S.F. 4 (Clara and John), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Ross C. Fisher, 215 West 6th St., LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Robert J. Gans, 440 N. Las Palmas Av., LA 4 (Bob), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Robert S. Odell, 745 Market St., S.F. (Bob), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J. T. Woods, P.O. Box 7844, Duvalle St., LA 15 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Charles Q. Sunderlin, 10042 S. Wilton, LA 47, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Biff Smith, Box 55, Boron Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. W.C. Berry, 3747 - 20th St., S.F. Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Paul C. Alexander, 626 Powell St., S.F., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J. Dearth, 298 Upper Terrace, S.F. (Jack and Julia), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Felix Juda, 300 Van Nuys Bldg., LA 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Bishop Robert B. Gooden, 1629 Santa Maria Av., Glendale 8 (Dear Bishop Gooden), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Ben M. Kochman, 215 W. 5th St., LA 13 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Paul Hallingby, Jr., 2 Rector St., N.Y. 6, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - John M. Hanley, P. O. Box 342, Palo Alto, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Samuel L. Fendel, District Grand Lodge No. 4 Bnai Brith, 593 Market St., S.F. 5 (Sam), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. Twain Michelsen, Superior Court, S.F. (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - William A. White, Department Commander, American Legion, War Memorial, Veterans Bldg., S.F. 2) (Bill), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Richard Lane, 408½ N. La Cienega, LA 48 (Dick), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. C. Maddux, Bakersfield-Friends - 1740, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable John Francis Neylan, 1 Montgomery St., S.F. (Jack), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Henry F. Petersen, 52 Pierce St., S.F. 17, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Bruce A. Findley, Associate Superintendent L.A. City Schools, 450 N. Grand L.A. and, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Benjamin W. Vallat, 1158 Chautauqua Blvd., Pacific Palisades (Ben), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. John J. Allen, Jr., House of Representatives, Washington D.C. (Carol and John), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. John Middleton Holmes, 630 N. Orange Drive., LA (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. Charles W. Meyers, 417 Fort Blvd., S.F. (Arlene and Charlie), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. John Hanlon, 126 - 10th Ave., San Mateo Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Clifford Johnson, Arbuckle, Calif. (Irene and Doctor, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. A.A. Erhart, Pismo Beach (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - C.N. Giere, M.D., 2901 Capitol Ave., Sacramento Doctor, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - John F. Feldmeier, c/o Sierra Title Co., San Andreas, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Charles Luther Bogue, Del Mar, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Ethel A. Dunn, General Delivery 52, L.A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Robert L. Jordan, 5201 Wilshire Blvd., LA 36 (Helen and Bob), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Goldie Brewer, P. O. Box 27, Auburn, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Gustave A. Jahn, 1805 Valle Vista Drive, Redlands (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. George L. Humphreys, Chairman, Board of Trustees, 502 Homer Laughlin Bldg. 315 S. Broadway, LA 13, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Woodrow Miller, Colton, Calif. (Woody), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Paul T. Mannen, P. O. Box 578, Del Mar, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - S. Tilden Norton, President, wilshire Boulevard Temple, Wilshire & Hobart Bl LA 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. William J. Blackstock, 630 Santiago Ave., North Sacramento (Bill), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Lee Breckinridge Thomas, 2747 Haste St., Berkeley, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - meyer Lewis, Flotill Products, Stockton, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dwight H. Hart, Jr., Manager, The Clift Hotel, S.F., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Ed Clancy, California Medical Association, 417 S. Hill St., LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Frank F. Sebastian, 2808 Santa Paula Court, Sacramento, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Milton Gitelson and Family, 2650 Benedict Canyon, Beverly Hills Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Manny Harmon, 1132 Cory Ave., LA 46 (Rosalee and Manny), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Carl W. Gross, LA 810 S. norton ave, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. E. G. Jefferies 411 N. Heliotrope Dr., Hollywood 4 Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. A.H. Baker, 6900 S. Shore Drive, Chicago 49, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Elizabeth Foreman, 1200 S. Citrus, LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dr. Hugo E. Apel, LA Doctor - 146½ h., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Joseph Tanzola, Corresponding Secretary, St. Anne's Maternity Hospital Guild, 155 N. Occidental Blvd., LA 26, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Henry Gilbert, LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Joseph R. GRILLO 9401 Victoria Av., South Gate Friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Samuel J. Rothman, 605 West Olympic Blvd., LA 15 (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. K. D. Brown, credit manager, 5600 Wilshire Blvd., LA 36, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Alfred W. Robertson, 3263 Cliff Drive, Santa Barbara (Robby and Marilyn), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Isidor Gelberg, 528 S. Main St., LA 13, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Hutton, 805 S. Ogden Drive, LA 36, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Miss Martha Meis, 3618½ Stocker St., LA 8, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Carlson, 2917 - W. 15th St., LA 6 (Betty and Arthur), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Frank J. Buckley, 334 S. Muir field Road, LA 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Ronald E. Kaehler, Stock Exchange Bldg., S.F.4 (Ron), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Leo J. Knight, 190 S. 2nd E., Provo, Utah (Leo), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. C. EDWARD Beaumont, 9326 Sawyer St., LA 35 (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Blanche Mydland, 9316 - 2nd Ave., Inglewood, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Charles F. Van de Water, Sr, 4130 Chestnut Ave., L.B. 7, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mae Cushman, 1130 W. 53rd St., LA 37, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Herbert White, 12450 Rossmore, LA (Priscilla and Herbert), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Clem Randau, Hotel Stockton, Stockton (Bea and Clem), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Dan O. Kilroy, 3300 Third Ave., Sacramento 17 (Dear Friends:), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Alan Wilder, Astrology Editor, Southern California Associated Newspapers Box 2270, Hollywood 28, California, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - William J. Mc Nichols, 6404 Hollywood Blvd., L.A. 28 (Bill), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - George W. Rochester, Attorney at Law, 639 S. Spring Street, LA 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Wesley S. KOHTZ, 1317 W. 80th St., L.A. (Dear Wesley and Family), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Howard E. Crandall, 1614 Marine Ave., Wilmington, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. William C. Doran and Family, California State Bldg., LA 12 (Dear Bill and Family), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. Floyd, 625 S., B. A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Virginia Carlson, 952 S. Gramercy Place, LA 19, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. LYNN Bernheim, 9414 W. Olympic Blvd., Beverly Hills, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Ruth E. Roehrs, 6534 Hayes Drive, LA 48, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. John F. Thompson, R.R. #3, Box 408, San Jose (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Horace R. Lamb, 15 Broad Street, New York, N.Y. (Hod), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. O. Swanson, 2044 S. Horne Street, Oceanside, Calif. (Odeta), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Calvin Collins, 977 Middle Rincon, Santa Rosa, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Sherman Macdonald, 27 LABURNUM Rd., Atherton, Calif., Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Honorable and Mrs. R.R. Cunningham, P. O. Box 582, Hanford, Calif. friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Harry L. Ryberg, D.C. 1787 Santa Cruz Ave., Menlo Park, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Timothy Manning, Auxiliary Bishop of Los Angeles, 1531 W. 9th St., LA 15 (Dear Bishop Manning), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Series 4. Condolences, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
    Box
  - Mrs. Fred Roberts and Family, 350 East Jefferson Blvd., LA friends, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Josephine Woods and Helen Jane Gingery, 927 S. Woods, LA. (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - California State Apartment Conference, 3923 W. 6th St., L.A. 5 Attention: P.J. O'Donovan, Secretary-Treasurer Mr. O'Donovan, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - G. Stanley Gordon, M.D., 17003 Ventura Blvd., Encino Doctor, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Vernon C. Dargan, 704 S. Spring St., LA 14, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Patrick Henry Phillips, 2845 San Marino, LA 6 (Pat), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - A. Waite, 425 Bush St., S.F. 4 Ed, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Donald H. McKee, 900 Wilshire Blvd., LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Howard E. Deems, Villa Riviera Apts., L.B. (Norine and Howard), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Martin Mc Manus, Jr. 3994 Cherrywood Ave., LA 8, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. Jerrold L. Seawell, 303 Mariposa St., Roseville (Mildred), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.W. Knight, P. O. Box 37, Provo, Utah (Jennie and Will), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. N.L. Levering, 440 Base Line, San Bernardino (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - The Chevaliers, Chevalier's Book Store, 239 N. Larchmont, LA (Dear Friends), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Mark C. Bloome, 717 N. Sierra Drive, Beverly Hills (Eva and Mark), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. James Buchanan, 1548 N. Columbus Ave., Glendale (Ruth and Jim), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Barbara Lux Mac Bride, 101 S. Sycamore Ave., Apt. 6, LA 36, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Clark S. Teitsworth, 26 Broadway, N.Y. 4, N.Y. (Crack), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. T. G. Sylva, San Pedro -, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. R. Marshall, Arlington, California (Bob and Myrtle), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Sam David, 212 W. First St., LA, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. C.S. Thompson, 1520 Maple Street, South Pasadena (Esther and Charles), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Charles Edwards, 18601 Plummer St., Northridge (Isobel and Charles), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Russell Wood Starr, M.D., 1926 Eighth Ave., LA 18 Doctor, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mrs. A.J. Wallace, Jr., LA (Peggy), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - William J. Silva, Commissioner, 1116 H Street, Modesto, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Mr. and Mrs. G.E. Oaks, Redding (Marjorie and Grover), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Hon. George J. Hatfield, State Senator, P.O.Box 818, Newman, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Juanita Walker, 627 North Spaulding, LA 36, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Nick De Meo, 1505 Jewell Drive, Santa Rosa, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Hampton Hutton, Attorney at Law, 453 S. Spring Street, LA 13, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)
  - Edgar C. Levey, Attorney at Law, 593 Market St., S.F. 5, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175)